<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Chris Carmichael</title>
    <link>https://www.chris-carmichael.dev/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Chris Carmichael</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 04:27:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.chris-carmichael.dev/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 Python3 and Ansible</title>
      <link>https://www.chris-carmichael.dev/blog/2020/01/11/2020-python3-ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 04:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chris-carmichael.dev/blog/2020/01/11/2020-python3-ansible/</guid>
      <description>2020 Python 3 - Leave the Past Behind It&#39;s 2020, and Guido warned us long ago that Python 2 was being deprecated. The biggest issue is no more security updates for Python 2. Security is important, don&#39;t ya think?
Time to make some upgrades and mods.
Install Python 3 I already had this installed, but finding instructions is easy to do. This write-up from vitux.com looks pretty good.
# install the bitssudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt install python3 -yPython Alternatives - Default to Python 3 in Bash You&#39;ll want to change the default behavior of your machine to use Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AnsibleFest 2019 Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://www.chris-carmichael.dev/blog/2019/09/27/ansiblefest-2019-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 08:43:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chris-carmichael.dev/blog/2019/09/27/ansiblefest-2019-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>AnsibleFest 2019 Thoughts I attended the Ansible conference again this year, and it didn&#39;t disappoint. Almost every session I sat in showcased deep technical content presented by seasoned engineers. Many of them are folks in the field without any corporate sponsorship or agenda. Just techies solving difficult problems using modern automation tooling, which is exactly what I look for in a conference.
Here are the most interesting topics I took from the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging With Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.chris-carmichael.dev/blog/2019/09/05/blogging-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 07:28:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chris-carmichael.dev/blog/2019/09/05/blogging-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Time to Blog I&#39;ve been into computers for over 30 years, since I was a teenager taking apart a Tandy 1000 EX. Yikes my mom was so mad. She threatened to take a broom to my good friend Jason and I if we didn&#39;t have it put back together by the morning. We succeeded, and I&#39;ve been addicted to technology ever since.
Professionally, I&#39;ve got ~20 years of experience. I recently had an opportunity to land an evangelist job talking about kubernetes, but the hiring manager couldn&#39;t find me online.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>